It feel so good
that I'm able to witness this.
Even her priorities have shifted.
What's improtant to you have become
important to her as well.
I hope I can witness
your mission accomplished.
To achieve that simple life.
Thank you.
Angelito has been sleeping all this time.
Will he still be able to wake up?
I will do everything I can, Sofie.
Just believe.
Agents, be ready. You know what to do.
Who is this?
Where?
It's us!
Hold on.
Sianong?
Sianong.
Duh?
I didn't train in martial arts
and boxing just to back down from a fight.
They're just guns.
Aren't you scared?
I am.
I won't die without putting up a fight.
Sofie.
I'll help you.
-Angelito,
don't push yourself.
Your body isn't ready yet.
Lady Amor.
Please take care of Angelito.
I'll handle the enemies.
Sofie!
Daddy Sir.
Come here!
Come here! Come with me!
Let me go!
Angelito!
Sofie, my child!
Daddy Sir!
How are you?
Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay, Daddy Sir.
You're safe now.
Let's get out of here.
-Rafa.
-Come on.
Help Angelito.
Let's go.
Come on, Sofie.
I'm out of ammo.
I still have some.
I'm out too.
Agent Sianong!
-Agent Sianong, your body can't take it.
-Let me fight.
You need to rest.
We'll take it from here.
Get down!
General Norberto, where's Angelito?
Over there, in the vehicle.
Angelito!
Alex!
-Angelito.
-Sianong!
-Angelito!
Angelito!
Wake up!
-Dara.
-Hurry! Hurry!
-Wait…
-Bok! Bok!
You can do it, Bok.
I've got him.
Easy, easy.
Move! Move! Move!
Angelito.
Wake up!
Help!
Angelito, I'm sorry.
-Angelito.
Help!
Hey, help!
Angelito.
How's the patient, Doc?
Thank you, Doc.
Alex.
Doc. How's Angelito?
Thank you, Doc.
But…
we still have a bigger problem.
La Morte Bianca.
Mikoy.
You don't have to come.
Stay with your brother.
keep me updated.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Don't worry, sweetheart.
I'll be back soon.
Let's go.
John.
Take the knight.
Dummy!
I said take it with the bishop!
I have good news.
Everyone's safe.
-Yes!
-Really?
Thank God.
Can I please see them?
Or at least talk to them?
Please lend me a phone.
Just so I can talk to them.
Yes!
I'm sorry, Ma'am Tess.
I can request it from the agency, but…
I can't promise they'll approve it.
That's unfair.
But, Officer,
I hope you understand.
Don't you have parents too? A mother?
Who's the first person
you call when you're sick?
-Isn't it your mother?
-He's right, bro.
Just imagine
Tess was your mother.
Just imagine.
Children matter to their mothers.
So let Ma'am Tess talk to Mikoy.
He's right, boss.
If Ma'am Tess gets sick, it'll be on you.
I'll be held accountable
if I violate protocol.
The rules are clear. No phones.
You already snuck in a cellphone.
I didn't even report you.
It's the same thing.
You'll be accountable if you allow Tess.
You'll be accountable
if you break protocol.
So do the right thing.
He's right, son.
Please!
Fine.
But if I get in trouble for this,
you're all coming down with me.
All clear.
Thank you so much, son.
Hey, that knight's still hanging.
Boss, you seem a little hot.
Do you know what they call it
when Ben gets sick?
-What?
Sick-si-Ben.
Mikoy, my son.
My dear Mikoy.
Mikoy, my son!
Mikoy, how are you?
Are you hurt? Let me see.
Mom, how did you get a phone?
Never mind that. How are you?
I'm perfectly fine.
You know I'm an action star now.
And I take after Dad.
Those enemies are no match for me, Mom.
That's right.
Besides, I'm the son
of the Butuan Executioner.
Oh, stop that.
I don't like hearing about executioners.
Didn't your father leave the service
so we could have a peaceful life?
I just want my cheerful Mikoy.
That's all I want, son.
Mom.
I'm still your cheerful Mikoy.
I've just learned how to fight now.
I'm still cheerful, just more fearless.
That's it.
I'm glad you haven't changed, son.
Of course, Mom.
You raised Angelito and I well.
How's Angelito? What did the doctor say?
Angelito…
Mom, Mom, relax.
Angelito's okay.
Okay?
They said he's stable.
The doctor said
his radiation exposure wasn't that severe.
He just needs plenty of rest.
Thank God.
You know, son,
I think I prayed to every saint
just to keep you safe.
When will this all end?
I just want all of this to be over.
But Mom,
this will only end
once we defeat La Morte Bianca.
And it won't be easy.
Storms don't last forever.
This storm will pass too.
Just have faith, Mom.
I love you, Mom.
Bye-bye, son.
Take care, son.
there's been no word from Los Bandidos
since they launched their surprise attack
on La Morte Bianca's fortress.
they're already dead.
That's what I was thinking too.
We'll only lose more men.
By then, we could all be dead.
Before we can even get the bomb,
we might all be dead.
We're not in checkmate yet.
The Wacka-Wacka Initiative
The bomb is her trump card.
What do you mean?
She'll make her move.
She'll exploit people's weaknesses.
And she'll use the bomb
as her insurance policy.
So she can do whatever she wants.
And once that happens,
once it turns into war,
or chaos like a pandemic,
who will people turn to for protection?
La Morte Bianca?
What happened?
Why are they shooting each other?
Where did they get those guns?
Looks like La Morte Bianca
has made her move.
I know someone who can help us.
Another assassin.
Who?
Stop distracting me.
Don't you know I'm good at lip-reading?
Don't be so negative. I'm concentrating.
What did she say?
She said he'll be coming in soon.
Then she'll torture us.
Oh.
I told you so.
Ouch!
Do whatever you want.
I'm here outside the facility.
Agent Alex, for Chiara Valtrovi.
For me?
How did she know where to send the box?
I thought it's top secret information
and only the agents can know.
Someone is leaking information
to the enemy.